[
  {
    "questionNo": 1,
    "question": " How many seashells did Ada and Charles collect together?<br>(16 + 12 = ?)",
    "options":["1","6","","","",""],
    "operand": "+",
    "answers": ["1","6","1","2","2","8"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 2,
    "question": "How many clues do they have in total if they found hidden clues while digging?<br>(23 + 14 = ?)",
    "options":["","","1","4","",""],
    "operand": "+",
    "answers": ["2","3","1","4","3","7"]
    
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 3,
    "question": " How many crabs did they still see after some scuttled away?<br>(22 - 11 = ?)",
    "options":["2","2","","","",""],
    "operand": "-",
    "answers": ["2","2","1","1","1","1"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 4,
    "question": "How many seashells does Ada have after giving some to Charles?<br>(18 - 07 = ?)",
    "options":["","","0","7","",""],
    "operand": "-",
    "answers": ["1","8","0","7","1","1"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 5,
    "question": "Ada saw 15 dolphins while Charles spotted 14. How many dolphins did they see in total?<br>(15 + 14 = ?)",
    "options":["1","5","","","",""],
    "operand": "+",
    "answers": ["1","5","1","4","2","9"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 6,
    "question": "They found 34 golden coins but lost some while running back. Help them count how many coins they have now.(34 - 11 = ?)",
    "options":["3","4","","","",""],
    "operand": "-",
    "answers": ["3","4","1","1","2","3"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 7,
    "question": "After collecting 27 colorful stones, Ada gave away some. How many colorful stones does she have left?<br>(27 - 06 = ?)",
    "options":["","7","0","","",""],
    "operand": "-",
    "answers": ["2","7","0","6","2","1"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 8,
    "question": "How many pieces of treasure do they have now after finding more?<br>(22 + 13 = ?)",
    "options":["2","2","","","",""],
    "operand": "+",
    "answers": ["2","2","1","3","3","5"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 9,
    "question": "ow many starfish did they find in total after spotting more?<br>(21 + 08 = ?)",
    "options":["","","0","8","",""],
    "operand": "+",
    "answers": ["2","1","0","8","2","9"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 10,
    "question": "How many more minutes do they have left for their hunt?<br>(40 - 20 = ?)",
    "options":["4","0","","","",""],
    "operand": "-",
    "answers": ["4","0","2","0","2","0"]
  }
]
